(リー)目的地は まだですか？
Are we getting close
to our destination?
(パックン)このぶんだと 到着するのは
明日の昼頃だろう… って…➡
At this rate, we'll get there
around noon tomorrow.
Stop asking me the same question
every five minutes!
５分ごとに同じ質問するのは➡
やめんかい！
わっ…。
(テンテン)リー
焦ったって しょうがないわ。
Lee, don't be so antsy!
What are you saying?! Our comrades
are anxiously waiting for us!
何を言っているんです！
里の仲間が ボクたちの到着を
心待ちにしているんですよ！
熱血フルパワーで
一刻も早くたどり着くのが➡
Our mission is to move at full speed
and get there as soon as possible!
ボクらの使命です！
(パックン)とんだ空回り野郎じゃな…。
You waste so much energy...
(いの)シズネ先輩。
Shizune Senpai...
Hmm?
If the enemy has made contact
with the Three-Tails...
敵が三尾と接触したってことは…。
That means they have a Jutsu
相手にも 三尾を手に入れる術が
あるってことですよね。
to take the Three-Tails
into their possession, right?
(シズネ)そうね。 封印術か
私たちの知らない未知の術か…。
Yes. Probably a Sealing Jutsu,
or some Jutsu we don't know about.
こっちも到着次第 すぐに
封印にとりかからないと…。
Once we get there, we'll have to use
our Sealing Jutsu immediately.
先を越されるわけにはいかないわ。
We can't have them beat us to it.
では 決まりですね！
Then it's decided!
Let's pick up our pace to twice,
no, three times the speed!
今までの２倍 いや
３倍のスピードで飛ばしましょう！
はぁ… また そういうムチャを…。
Not that nonsense again...
でも その心意気は買うわ。
パックン お願い！
But I fully agree.
Pakkun, lead the way!
仕方ないな。 みんな 遅れるなよ！
Seems I have no choice.
Everyone, don't fall behind!
(ヤマト)ハッ！
まっ こんなもんでしょ…
どうです？ 先輩。
Well, that's about it.
What do you think, Senpai?
Yeah, looks good.
(カカシ)うん いいんじゃない。
さっきから
全然 ページが進んでいませんね。
You haven't turned a page in a while.
Is something on your mind?
何か考えごとでも？
ん？
Hmm?
まっ いろいろとね。
Oh, this and that...
なぁ ヤマト。
Yamato, how do you think those guys
intended to capture the Three-Tails?
ヤツらはどうやって 三尾を捕まえる
つもりだったんだと思う？
そうですね。
なにぶん 相手は尾獣…。
Well, it's a Tailed Beast, after all...
敵の晶遁は強力ですが➡
Our opponent's Crystal Style
is powerful,
それだけで
押さえ込める相手じゃない…。
but I doubt that it's enough
to suppress the Tailed Beast...
とすると 何か並行して
他の手段を用意していた？
Which means they must use
another measure concurrently.
(カカシ)だが あの時➡
But back then, we weren't restrained
for very long.
オレたちが足止めされていた時間は
そう長くなかったはずだ。
I can't believe that they were able
その間に連中が
大掛かりな術式の準備が➡
to prepare for such
an elaborate formula in that time.
出来たとは考えにくい…。
確かに… そういえば
ナルトが湖で子供を見たって…。
That's true...
But didn't Naruto say he saw
a child by the lake?
やっぱ 気になるよね…。
That bothers me...
それに あの晶遁使いとも➡
On top of that, we'll be facing
that Crystal Style user very soon...
またすぐに やり合わなきゃ
いけないんだろうし…。
どちらへ？
Where are you going?
さしあたって
今 出来ることをね。
Let's analyze the situation and
do whatever we can now.
(ヒナタ)カカシ先生…。
Kakashi Sensei...
Let me interrupt for a little.
Hey, I want to discuss something.
ちょっと ジャマするよ。
おい 少し話をしたいんだが…。
(シノ)あぁ…。
Okay...
Everyone's Feelings
((あのね… 紅蓮さんが
ボクの帰る場所… なんだ…))
Umm...you're the one I come back to.
帰る場所か…。
Come back to...huh...?
I wonder where he went.
(ナルト)アイツ…
どこにいるんだってばよ。
He's from the Hidden Leaf...
コイツ… たしか木ノ葉の…。
It'll be a bother if he gets any closer.
これ以上 近づかれても面倒だな。
Don't move from this spot.
ここを動くなよ。
(キバ)交代の時間だぜ。
I'm here to relieve you.
Right. So far, there's been
nothing unusual.
(サクラ)了解。 今のところ
特に異常はないわ。
- Um... Sakura...
- Huh?
(サイ)あの… サクラ。
- Sai?
- Hey!
サイ？
(キバ)おい お前の担当は
ここじゃないだろ。
This isn't your position.
Oh, I know that, but...
(サイ)いえ
それはわかっているんですが…。
ナルト 知りませんか？
Do you know where Naruto is?
Huh? Isn't he in his assigned spot?
え？ 持ち場にいない？
Well, I don't see him.
それが 姿が見えなくて…。
That guy, did he go back early?
アイツ 先に戻ったのか？
If so, we would've crossed paths...
だったら
途中で すれ違うはずだし…。
That's right. Even Naruto would
wait to be relieved of duty...!
そうよ。 いくらナルトだって➡
引き継ぎくらいは… まさか…。
No way...
If that wave took him,
there wouldn't be any trace left...
あの波に流されたんだ。
やっぱ 痕跡なんて
あるわけねえか。
Who are you?!
誰だ！
感謝しな。
You should be grateful!
I came just for you.
わざわざ こちらから
出向いてやったんだ。
You're...
テメエは…。
１人で ノコノコと…。
Lurking around all by yourself...
If your purpose was to spy,
you came across the worst opponent.
偵察のつもりだろうが
出会った相手が悪かったね。
どうやら
これは幻覚じゃねえみてえだな。
It seems this is no illusion...
Crystal Style: Jade Crystal Blade!
結晶翠晶刀！
Die!
死にな！
はぁ～っ！
I'm not spying!
オレは 偵察にきたんじゃねえ。
捜しにきたんだってばよ！
I'm searching!
お前と一緒にいた あのチビをな！
For that kid who was with you!
答えろ！ アイツは どこにいる？
Answer me! Where is he?!
Guren...?
紅蓮さん？
ボク… 行かなくちゃ。
I...have to go.
なんだって!? ナルトが消えた？
What?! Naruto has disappeared?
(ヤマト)
何者かに襲撃された可能性は？
What is the possibility that
he came under attack?
I didn't pick up
any suspicious scents at the site.
現場に 怪しいニオイは
残ってなかった。
どうもアイツ 勝手に
１人で行っちまったみたいで。
I think he just took off on his own.
He seemed to have something
on his mind...
そういえば 何か
考え込んでたみたいだったけど➡
こんなことするなんて…。
But to go off like this...
Naruto...
ナルト君…。
まったく…。
Geez... In any case, we have
to find Naruto at once.
とにかく早急に
ナルトを捜さないと。
Then we all...
じゃあ みんなで…。
(カカシ)いや 前にも言ったが➡
No, like I said before...
It's dangerous to go
into the fog recklessly.
むやみに霧の中に入るのは危険だ。
Yamato and I will search for him.
捜索には オレとヤマトで向かう。
(カカシ)口寄せの術！
Summoning Jutsu!
(ビスケ)
珍しいな オレが呼ばれるなんて。
It's very rare for you to summon me.
ちょっと パックンを
使いに出していてね。
Pakkun is out on a mission, so Biscuit,
I need you to find Naruto right away.
ビスケ すぐにナルトを追ってくれ。
わかった。
Gotcha.
シノとキバ ヒナタは 霧の外から➡
Shino, Kiba and Hinata
search outside the mist.
サクラとサイは
上空から探索にあたってくれ。
Sakura and Sai will do
aerial reconnaissance.
(サクラたち)はい！
絶対 単独行動はするな。
- Yes!
Do not act alone.
あのチビは どこにいる？
無事なんだろうな？
Where is the little kid?
Is he okay?!
This guy...
Why's he asking about Yuukimaru...?
《コイツ なぜ幽鬼丸のことを…。
そうか あれを見ていたのか》
I see... He was watching that...
Well, it's none of your business!
そんなこと お前に関係ないだろ！
It is my business!
関係あるってばよ！
フン！
So petty!
くだらん！
Tell me! I need to take him back!
答えろ！ オレはアイツを
連れ戻さなきゃならねえんだ！
Are you crazy?
バカじゃないのか？
連れ戻すもなにも➡
Take him back?
He was on our side from the beginning.
アイツは もともと
こっちの人間だよ。
No! It's my fault that
he went over to your side!
違う！ アイツが
そっちに行っちまったのは➡
オレのせいなんだ。 オレが
余計なことを言っちまったから。
All because of the unnecessary stuff
I said to him...
余計なこと？
Unnecessary?
ありがとう。
ボクに教えてくれたよね。
Thank you.
You taught me, didn't you?
Y-You...
お前…。
幽鬼丸…。
Yuukimaru...
思ってくれる人がいるところが
帰る場所なんだって。
Wherever someone thinks of you
is the place you go home to...
Hey, don't move!
おい 動くな！
I'm really grateful.
すごく感謝してるんだ ボク。
I finally found the place
where I can go back to.
やっと
帰る場所が見つかったんだよ。
Right, Guren?
ねっ 紅蓮さん。
ごめんな。
Sorry.
幽鬼丸！
動くな。
Yuukimaru!
Don't move!
影分身を１体 隠していたか。
So you were hiding one
of your Shadow Clones.
Guren!
紅蓮さん！
お前 幽鬼丸っていうんだな。
So your name is Yuukimaru?
オレはナルトだ。
ナルト…。
I'm Naruto.
Naruto...
Yuukimaru, you're going home
with me to Hidden Leaf Village.
幽鬼丸 お前はオレと一緒に➡
木ノ葉に帰るんだ。
どうして？
Why?
She's not the one you're going home to!
アイツは お前が帰る場所なんかじゃ
ねえからだ。
アイツは大蛇丸の手下だ。
She serves Orochimaru.
And this guy Orochimaru will
do anything to achieve his ambition.
大蛇丸ってヤツは 目的のためなら
どんなことだってする。
He's a bastard who thinks
nothing of taking peoples' lives.
人の命だって
何とも思わねえ クソ野郎だ。
Anyone who serves a guy like
that can't be a decent human being!
そんなヤツに ついてるようなヤツが➡
まともな人間なわけがねえ！
Guren will protect me...
(幽鬼丸)
紅蓮さんは ボクを守ってくれる。
優しくしてくれるし
思ってくれる。
She's kind to me and she thinks of me...
It's obvious she's just using you!
そんなの お前を
利用しようとしてるだけに➡
決まってんだろうが！
うるさい！
Shut up!
うわっ！
This kid won't return to your place!
コイツは お前のところには帰らない。
(幽鬼丸)紅蓮さん。
Guren...
Something's coming...
《何か来る…。
木ノ葉のヤツらか》
The Hidden Leaf...
I'm taking him by force, if necessary!
腕ずくでも連れ帰るってばよ！
結晶六角手裏剣乱舞！
Hexagonal Crystal Shuriken:
Wild Dance!
うわっ！ うっ！
What?!
なに!?
くらえ！
Take this!
うわっ！
逃がすか！ うっ…。
I won't let you get away!
Naruto, stop!
(カカシ)ナルト！ そこまでだ。
フゥ… 確保完了。
Stabilized and secured.
Let me go!
離してくれってばよ！
オレは アイツを…。
I'm taking him...!
It's no use. They've disappeared.
ムダだ。 ヤツらは もう消えたよ。
Damn it...
クソッ…。
((アイツは大蛇丸の手下だ。
She serves Orochimaru.
(人の命だって
何とも思わない クソ野郎だ))
He's a bastard who thinks
nothing of taking peoples' lives.
(牛頭)紅蓮さん おケガは？
Guren, are you hurt?
余計なことするな！
Don't bother me!
((アイツは お前が帰る
場所なんかじゃねえからだ))
She's not the one you're going home to.
《あのガキ 今度会ったら…》
That kid... When I see him again...
(牛頭)すみませんでした。 でも➡
I'm sorry... But...
あなたが無事で よかった。
I'm glad you're all right.
ハァ… ハァ…。
幽鬼丸！
Yuukimaru!
オレは帰るぞ。
あぁ ご苦労さま。
I'm going back.
Right. Thanks.
(ヤマト)どういうつもりだ？
勝手に行動すれば➡
What's with you?
Surely, you knew that if
you went off on your own,
あの晶遁使いと出くわす可能性が
あることくらい➡
you were bound to encounter
that Crystal Style user?
わかってたろ？
それは…。
I know.
でも オレ どうしてもアイツを…。
But I... I just had to find him...
言い訳は よせ！
Don't make excuses.
You're lucky; you could've
been dead by now.
運が悪ければ 今ごろキミは
死んでいたかもしれない。
感情で動いて
仲間たちを危険にさらして！
You put your comrades in danger
because you gave in to your emotions.
こんなことで キミを信じて
任務に出してくれた綱手様に➡
How can you face Lady Tsunade,
who put her trust in you and
sent you on this mission?
顔向けできるのかい？
悪かったってばよ。
Okay, I was wrong.
今回の任務は どう転ぶか
わからない危険な代物だ。
This mission involves a dangerous,
unpredictable foe.
個人の勝手な行動は
仲間を全滅させることもある。
Recklessly acting on your own
could spell death for everyone.
そのことを肝に銘じておけ。
あぁ。
Don't let yourself forget that.
Yeah.
じゃあ 戻りますか。
そうだな。
Shall we return?
Yes.
ところでナルト… お前
湖で子供を見たって言ってたな。
By the way, Naruto,
you said you saw a child at the lake.
え… それが？
気になることがある。
Huh? What about it?
Something's been bothering me.
Tell me the details of that incident.
その時のこと
もう少し詳しく聞かせてくれ。
(麟児)紅蓮さん よくご無事で…。
Guren! I'm glad you're okay.
すんません。 湖の近くじゃ
オレの探索網が使えなくて…。
Sorry. But I couldn't use my search net
near the lake.
まぁいい。
Forget it... It seems we haven't
lost any fighting strength...
どうやら こっちの戦力は
欠けてないようだね。
若干１名 欠けたほうが
よかったヤツもいるけどな。
Although, there's at least one
I would've preferred to lose.
悪運が強いのは お互いさまだろ。
So I'm blessed with the luck of evil.
It's mutual.
少し弱っているが許容範囲だな。
He's weakened, but it's tolerable.
疲れているんだ 休ませてやれ。
(カブト)残念だけど➡
He's exhausted. Let him rest.
Unfortunately...
ボクたちも そうのんびり
構えていられないみたいでね。
I don't think we can afford to
hang around here.
どう考えても 連中が三尾を
捕獲するという大事な場面に➡
I just can't imagine why those guys
would take an ordinary kid along,
ただの子供を連れていくとは
考えにくくてな。
when they face a huge challenge
in snaring the Three-Tails.
ただの子供じゃないって…。
He's no ordinary kid, I tell you...
例えば 三尾に対して何らかの
強制力を持っているとか…。
What if he possesses some
special power against the Three-Tails?
そういえば…。
Now that you mention it...
アイツが何かしたら
三尾の動きが止まったような…。
He did something and...
it seemed as though
the Three-Tails stopped moving.
やはりか…。
It figures...
人間が尾獣をコントロールしてた
ってことですか。
You mean a human was
controlling a Tailed Beast?
どんな手を使ったか知らないが
相手は あの大蛇丸だからな。
I don't know what trick they used,
but we're dealing with Orochimaru...
連中が子供を使って
三尾を捕獲する気なのは➡
It's probably no mistake
that they intend to use a child
to capture the Three-Tails.
間違いないだろう。
だとすると その子 このまま
放っておくわけにはいきませんね。
Which means, this child...
We can't just ignore him.
それって どういう意味だよ？
What do you mean by that?
スキを見て こちらで拘束する。
拘束？
We wait for an opportunity,
and then we take him.
Take him?
(カカシ)子供さえいなければ➡
As long as they don't have the boy,
they have no method to
capture the Three-Tails.
連中が三尾を手に入れる手段は
ないからね。
(ヤマト)それに大蛇丸が ただ三尾を
手に入れて満足するとは思えない。
And I can't believe that
Orochimaru will be satisfied with
just capturing Three-Tails...
遅かれ早かれ➡
Sooner or later,
自分にとって扱いやすい
人柱力を作ろうと考えるはずだ。
he'll think of ways to create
a Jinchuriki that is easy to control.
ヤツにとって 尾獣との
適応能力の高い子供は➡
For him, a boy with the ability
to synergize with a Tailed Beast
格好の素材になりかねない。
is merely a useful tool.
そんなこと させてたまっかよ！
I won't let him do that!
当然だ。
それに 里としても今後のため➡
You're absolutely right.
Besides, I'm sure they would want
to examine his powers back at the village.
彼の能力を調査しておきたいしな。
《まぁ すべては綱手様からの
返答があってからだが…》
Well, it all depends
on Lady Tsunade's reply.
ナルト!!
Naruto!
サクラちゃん！
Sakura!
クッ…。
これが 愛のムチってヤツか。
This is...the loving smack?
オレたちが説教するより
よっぽど効果的だな これは。
This is far more effective
than us trying to lecture him.
カカシ先生 ナルトには
キツく言い聞かせましたから。
Kakashi Sensei,
I gave Naruto an earful.
ちゃんと反省してた？
Was he sorry?
ご… ごめんなさい。
I'm so...sorry...
それより 朗報です。
Never mind that.
There's good news!
木ノ葉の増援が？
Reinforcements from the Hidden Leaf?
敵ながら対応が早い。 おそらく
ヤツら 三尾を封じにかかるだろう。
Our foes respond very quickly.
No doubt, they will try to seal
the Three-Tails.
冗談じゃない
三尾は大蛇丸様のものだ！
No way! The Three-Tails belongs
to Lord Orochimaru.
当然だよ。 だから紅蓮➡
Of course!
And that is why, this time, Guren...
キミには幽鬼丸を使って
今度こそ三尾をおさえてもらう。
You must use Yuukimaru
to suppress the Three-Tails.
しかし まだ幽鬼丸は…。
But Yuukimaru is still...
心配ない。 体力を底上げして
少し休ませれば また使えるさ。
Don't worry. If we build up his stamina
and allow him to rest a bit,
we'll be able to use him.
《また あの薬を飲ませるのか…》
He's going to give him that drug again...
だが 見たところ 幽鬼丸は
かなり衰弱しているようだ。
But Yuukimaru still looks awfully weak.
ムリをさせて ホントに大丈夫なのか？
If you force him...
Are you sure he'll be all right?
さぁ どうかな？
Well, I wonder...
Don't look at me like that.
そんなに怖い顔をするなよ。
キミだって承知しているはずだ。
You should know that Yuukimaru
is simply a tool to capture the Three-Tails.
幽鬼丸は
三尾を操作するためだけの道具。
今がんばってもらわないと
存在自体 意味がない。
Unless we make use of him now,
there's no meaning in
his very existence.
だが 今コイツが ぶっ壊れたら
計画は お釈迦になって…。
But if he collapses and the plan fails...
私の信用は まるつぶれだ！
My credibility will be totally ruined!
紅蓮 ボクだって
この計画の成功を望んでいるのさ。
Guren, I'm hoping that
the plan is a success.
だからこそ こうして…。
That's why I...
ムカツクねぇ！
Well, it's irritating.
You tend to stick your nose into
other people's business too often.
だいたいアンタ
人の仕事に口出しすぎなんだよ！
紅蓮… お前…。
Guren... You...
要は木ノ葉に三尾を
封印させなきゃいいんだろ。
The main thing is to prevent
the Hidden Leaf from sealing
the Three-Tails, right?
だったら 私が木ノ葉の連中を
殲滅してやる！
Well then, I'll destroy the Leaf!
もめたんですかい？
Had an argument?
あのクソメガネ もともと
気にくわないんだよ ったく！
I've never liked that four-eyed jerk!
幽鬼丸を殺す気なのか？
Does he want to kill Yuukimaru?
へぇ～。
Oh...
何だ!?
意外ですねぇ。
What?
It's unlike you to worry
so much about Yuukimaru.
紅蓮さんが
幽鬼丸の心配をするなんて。
ハッ バカ言うんじゃないよ。 私はただ
任務の心配をしているだけだ。
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm just concerned about our mission.
任務の心配ねぇ…。
Concerned about the mission, eh...?
増援が来たって 誰だってばよ？
(サクラ)まぁ 見ての お楽しみよ。
Reinforcements are here? Who?
Just wait and see.
もうダメじゃ… １歩も走れん。
I've had it... I can't run any further.
サクラちゃん 援軍って…。
Sakura, who's come to help...?
(いの)ナルト！
アンタ またムチャやったんだって？
You're so reckless, Naruto!
ドンマイです！
青春に ムチャはつきものです！
It's okay! Recklessness and youth
go hand in hand!
はい そこ！ 肯定しない！
Stop affirming his actions!
あっ！ お前ら！
Hey! You guys...!
Let me go over Lady Tsunade's orders.
Our new mission is to seal
the Tailed Beast, the Three-Tails.
And, to protect the child
from the enemy.
He seems to be connected
in some way to this Tailed Beast!
With the mission change,
you'll be divided into the following teams.
Sealing team, Guarding team
and the Crystal User Counter team.
Got it. And, how will we team up for this?
Yeah, about that... I have an idea.
Next time: "Regroup!"
Kakashi, I'm back now.
Oh, thanks.
"Oh thanks"? Can't you put
more appreciation into your reply?
ハァ ハァ…。 カカシ 今戻ったぞ。
あぁ ご苦労。
ご苦労って…。
In addition to my appreciation,
could you deliver another message?
感謝の気持を込めて言っても
バチは当たらんだろう。
Hey! Can't you be more kind to me?!
じゃあ 感謝ついでに悪いけど➡
Kakashi...Sensei.
もう ひとっ走り
伝令を頼まれてくれないか？
If you don't mind,
you can also use my
"Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll."
コラッ もっとワシをいたわらんか。
Huh?!
カカシ先生。 よかったら
ボクの超獣偽画を使ってください。
Information drawn by my ink
will change into small animals,
protect themselves,
and deliver messages outside.
ボクが墨で書いた情報は
小動物のように変化し➡
Oh, that's handy.
Then let's get to it.
自分の身を守りながら 情報を外へ
持ち出してくれますから。
- Wait a minute!
- Huh?
You can't trust scribble like that!
ほぅ ソイツは便利だな。 では 早速。
I'll show you what
Ninja Hounds are made of!
ちょっと待った！
ん？
そんな落書き 信用できるか！
I won't let an ink bird
take my chance to show off!
忍犬のほうが 優れておるところを
見せてやるわい！
Oh no. He's off...
《せっかくの拙者の出番➡
Did I do something wrong?
あんな墨鳥に取られてたまるか》
No. It's for the best.
あ～ぁ 行っちゃった。
ボク なにか悪いことしました？
Huh?
Oh no!
MAKE-OUT PARADISE
BEST QUOTE COLLECTION
I gave him the wrong scroll!
いや 結果オーライってことで。 ん？
Tune i
《しまった。 渡すの間違えた》